United States Council for International Business Records 6246
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Council for International Business Records
1981-1996
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Council for International Business (USCIB)
6246
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Papers.
6191565
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 07, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
United States Council for International Business
6191565
- Council for International Business. Papers., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Council for International Business. Papers., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Council for International Business. Papers., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Council for International Business. Papers., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Industrial Relations Committee. Minutes and Memorandums., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- International Labor Conference. Report., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- International Labor Conference. Report. (folder 1), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- International Labor Conference. Report. (folder 2), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Council for International Buisness Papers (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Scope and Contents
  US Council pamphlet. UK Speech: US Job Creation.